fxcash.com 2012-06-16

# FXCash : Privacy Policy - Forex Affiliate Program - Become an Affiliate - Forex and Binary Options - Privacy Policy - FXCash.

### FXCASH Privacy Policy

We are pleased to provide this privacy policy to inform you of our practices with respect to how we collect and use Personal Information (defined below) about visitors to the Site. We realize that the privacy of your personal information is very important and we will not treat this information in ways different from what is disclosed in this statement. By using this Site, you consent to the following terms.

## What We Collect

The information collected on fxcash.com is Publisher only related personally identifiable information and non-personally identifiable information. Forex Media Ltd is the sole owner of all the data collected on this site.

Publishers wishing to join the Fxcash Publisher Network are required to provide personally identifiable information including name, address, phone number, e-mail address.

We may also collect certain non-personally identifiable information. This information is anonymous; it is not connected with your personal information. Types of non-personally identifiable information we may collect, not exhaustive:

  * The URL that you came to our site from.
  * Your IP address at the time you visited our site.
  * Pages from our site you visited and time you spent at each page.

## What we do not collect:

We do not collect ANY personally identifiable information originating from advertising served by our clients. FXCASH acts as a third party solution provider and has NO access neither process any sort of information that could identify in any shape or form clients and/or prospects of products being advertised through our systems.

## Cookies

Cookies are small data files that a web site server stores on a computer. They contain information about activities performed by a user of the computer on the specific web site and characteristics of the computer at the time the user navigates the site. Examples: the IP address of the computer at the time the user navigates the site. As cookies are data files, not code, they cannot erase or read information from a computer's hard drive or from other sites the computer user visits. Cookies can only be read by the server of the site that set them, so that information about activities on one site can't be transferred through a cookie to another site.

We may store two types of cookies on your computer:

  * Session Cookies: These cookies are stored in the Internet browser and are deleted each time the browser is closed.We use session cookies mainly to facilitate sitenavigation: for example, once you log in to the site, youdon't have to log in again during the same session; andto personalize site experience.
  * Permanent Cookies: These cookies are stored on the hard drive of your computer. They are not exactly "permanent". Each cookie has different "life span" determined by theweb site that sets the cookie. We may use permanentcookies to store your username and password (encrypted)on your computer if you opt to have it saved.

We may use both types of cookies for aggregate audience analysis: where our visitors and Publishers come from, which pages they visit, how much time they spend on the site, etc. No personal information is stored in the cookies.

## Use of the Information

The Publisher personally identifiable information is used for business correspondence and for making payments to Publishers; it aids us to serve our Publishers in the most efficient and convenient way.

We use the non-personally identifiable information to enhance the functionality and usability of our site and to diagnose and prevent technical problems.

## Disclosure

FXCASH will not share Publishers personally identifiable information with any third parties except when required by law or as necessary to conduct business: to assist in normal and customary operational and statistical matters, or to provide administrative services such as billing and payments. If FXCASH or any of its assets are acquired by or merged with another entity, Publisher information will be one of the transferred assets.

## Links

In connection with the Site, we may provide links to certain third party websites or referrals to certain third parties’ products or services. If you choose to visit a third party’s website or use its products or services, please be aware that these third parties’ policies with respect to privacy, and not the fxcash privacy policy, will govern your activities and any information you disclose while interacting with these third parties. fxcash does not bear any responsibility for any actions or policies of such third party websites.

## Personal Information Updates

You may change certain of your Personal Information we have on file for you at any time by visiting the Edit Account page on the Site and making your desired changes.

## Personal Information Security

FXCASH uses both proprietary technology and methods in order to collect and store information. FXCASH has implemented technical and managerial procedures in order to protect Publishers personal information from unauthorized access and against loss, misuse or alteration.

However, due to the open nature of the Internet, no data transmission can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. Therefore, fxcash cannot warrant that the information stored on our servers or transmitted to or from a user will be absolutely safe and fxcash disclaims any liability for any theft or loss, unauthorized access or damage, or interception of any data or communications.

Your information may be stored and processed in the United States or any other country in which fxcash or its affiliates, subsidiaries or agents maintain facilities, and by using the Fxcash.com site, you consent to any such transfer of information outside of your country.

## No Information Collected from Children

In compliance with the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA) we will never knowingly collect any personal information about children under the age of 13. If we obtain indication that we have collected personal information about a child under the age of 13, that information will be immediately deleted from our database.

## Changes to Privacy Policy

By using the site you acknowledge your acceptance of our Privacy Policy. FXCASH reserves the right, at our only discretion to change, add or remove portions of this policy at any time. Please check this page periodically for changes. Your continued use of our site following the posting of changes to these terms will mean you accept those changes.

**Contact Information:**  
Forex Media Ltd   
57 Rue du Rhône  
1211 Geneva  
Switzerland  
Telephone: +41225349228  
Facsimile: +41225948376
